jomniaga.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy - Ashadee

**Web Form Information**

When you submit information to ashadee to make a payment or open an account, we may collect personally identifiable information from you that may include your name, address, email address, and credit card number. We do not knowingly collect personal information from persons under the age of eighteen.

**Website Usage Information**

We automatically collect IP addresses and website usage information from you when you access any of our online services. This information helps us evaluate how our visitors and subscribers use and navigate our websites on an aggregate basis, including, but not limited to, the number and frequency of visitors and subscribers to each web page and the length of their visits.

**How We Use Information Collected**

We may use information in the following ways:

  * To perform the actions for which you specifically provided the information (for example, enabling us to process, validate, and verify purchases).
  * To register you as a client and establish an account for you.
  * To send you email notifications about our new or existing ashadee products and services, special offers, or to otherwise contact you.
  * To enhance existing features or develop new features, products and services.
  * To provide advertisers and other third parties with aggregate information about our user base and usage patterns.
  * To allow us to personalize the content and advertising that you and others see based on personal characteristics or preferences.

Except as specifically set forth in this Privacy Policy, we will not share, sell, rent, or trade your personally identifiable information with any entity outside of ashadee for promotional purposes.

We may disclose and use personally identifiable information in special circumstances where it is necessary to enforce our service agreements or terms of use (for example, to protect our intellectual property rights). We may also disclose or use your personal information when we, in good faith, believe that the law may require us to do so.

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website.

**Orders**

If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email or shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date).

We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.

**Updating Personally Identifiable Information**

If your personally identifiable information changes you may request the information be corrected, updated, amended, or deleted through our [Contact Us page](http://support.jomniaga.com/) or by contacting us at the contact information listed below. We will respond to your request within 30 days.

**Information Collection**

ashadee automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookies, and the pages you request. This data is only used in the aggregate. ashadee uses information for the following general purposes: products and services provisioning, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, research, and anonymous reporting. IP addresses are automatically reported by your browser each time you view a web page. IP addresses may be used for various research purposes.

**Cookies**

We define a cookie as any string of data that is automatically stored on your computer upon access to our online services. ashadee employs cookies to assign temporary identification numbers to machines that access our web servers. This information enables us to deliver faster service to our users, prevent Denial of Service attacks on our systems, detect and prevent fraudulent transactions, and assist with awarding proper sales credit to our partners. All ashadee cookies are 1) of limited duration, 2) less than 5KB in length, 3) only visible to ashadee web servers, and 4) devoid of any personally identifiable information.

Third parties also use cookies and other tracking technologies on our site, of which data is only collected in the aggregate.

**What and How Information is Used**

ashadee may send you email notifications about our new or existing ashadee products and special offers specific to you. Out of respect for your privacy, you can unsubscribe by clicking "unsubscribe" within the email. You may not opt-out of service-related communications, which are not promotional in nature.

**Policy on Information Sharing**

Outside of the vendor who participated in your transaction, we will not sell, rent, share, or trade your personal information to third parties for promotional purposes. It may be necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, if required by law. In some cases, ashadee may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. ashadee will transfer information about you if we are acquired by or merged with another company.

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website.

**Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information such as credit card number on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using SSL.

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personally identifiable information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

The information we collect about you is stored in limited access servers. We maintain safeguards to protect the security of these servers and your personally identifiable information. We retain personally identifiable information only as long as necessary to complete a purchase, thwart fraud, or provide customer service.

**Newsletters**

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter, we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, you can unsubscribe by clicking "unsubscribe" within the email.

**Agents/Service Providers**

We use other third parties such as a database backup provider to protect our data, a fraud prevention service, and an email service provider to send out emails on our behalf.When you sign up for these services, we will share your personal information as necessary for the third party to provide that service.

**Blogs and Testimonials**

If you use a bulletin board, blog, or open forum on this website, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there may be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. We also have testimonials on our site, which post personally identifiable information. All individuals who have posted their testimonials have given permission to do so as a client.

**Links to Other Sites**

If you click on a link to a third party site you will leave our site and go to the site you selected. Because we cannot control the activities of third parties, we cannot accept responsibility for any use of your personally identifiable information by such third parties, and we cannot guarantee that they will adhere to the same privacy practices as us. We encourage you to review the privacy statements of any other service provider from whom you request services.

**Changes in this Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on your Account Home page.

**Comments and Questions**

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our Privacy Policy, you may contact us by submitting your inquiry to our [Customer Service Department](http://support.jomniaga.com/) or:

To reach us by fax, please dial: +603-7954-5277.

To reach us by mail, please use the following address:

Ashadee Sdn Bhd,  
No3B, Second Floor, Jalan 14/20,   
Seksyen 14, 46200 Petaling Jaya,   
Selangor, Malaysia.
